Lucia Lisdero

FullStack Developer React.js & Node.js

Buenos Aires city -Argentina (+54) 9 1126601086

lulisdero20@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/lulisdero github.com/Lulisderoo20

Full Stack Developer with a background in marketing and customer and employee experience, which helped me learn to lead and motivate a team, reach customers, eliminate any limit in terms of marketing, overcome my human values, gain charisma and fall in love every day more with the service to my team. Specialized in Back-end. Knowledge in agile methodologies, GIT, data structure, algorithms, and CSS frameworks. Experience in Front End and Back End development with React.js and Node.js. With good conflict resolution, motivation on a personal level and to third parties, interest in new tools and frameworks, interest in respect between human beings, human values, and a lot of enthusiasm to be part of a team in the technology industry. English level: C1 (Advanced).

PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - MR Properties June 2023

- July 2023

Academic experience. Henry Bootcamp

Page developed for a real estate agency with the aim of facilitating the sale of its properties both for its clients and for the real estate. This project was developed as a team with the students of the Henry Academy as a final project of the bootcamp.

Functions:

- Design interfaces and frontend elements, maintain and optimize websites and interfaces.
- Develop landing pages, dashboards and online applications on the Backend side using Node.js, express.js, Sequelize, Thunder Client and PostgreSQL
- Organize tasks with Trello.
- Organize meetings.
- Develop, maintain and optimize the implemented payment gateway.

Front: React js, Next 13 Back: Node.js, Express.js

Database: PostgreSQL and Sequelize.

github.com/Lulisderoo20

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

QA Manual, Digitizer and Technical Support

April 2021 - March 2022.

ZoomAgri, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Analyze the UI experience.
- Point out possible improvements.
- Resolve conflicts that prevent proper functioning in development and production.

• Maintain the proper functioning of the page.

Full Stack Henry Hero

April 2023 - June 2022.

Academic experience. Henry Bootcamp

- Teach virtual classes for initial students.
- Resolve doubts in the different channels of communication with students.
- Lead classes and instruct new teachers.

Fullstack Developer en Pigma Studio

Sep 2022 - actualidad.

Webpages development.

- Web design.
- Develop systems and tools with emphasis on performance and scalability, maintain databases, functional and technical documents.

TECHNOLOGIES:

Programming Languages: JavaScript **Framework Tools**: React.js, Node.js, Express.js **Database:** PostgreSQL and Sequelize. **Tools:** Git, Slack, Trello, Zoom, VSC. **Agile:** Scrum.

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

• Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 800 hours of theoretical-practical course. 2023.

COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION

• Javascript in Freecodecamp.org 2020.

LANGUAGES

- English C1 Advanced
- Portuguese Basic